HOSAM AL-REHANI

Full-stack web developer and unity developer



INFO:

Address:

Erbil

Phone:

+964 751 149 0237

Email:

Hosamre94@gmail.com

Website:

https://hosam.xyz

LinkedIn:

https://linkedin.com/in/hosam-rehani-903609bb

SKILLS:

.Net Core	95%
MSSQL / MySQL / MongoDB	65%
JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS	95%
React	65%
Unity	95%
Photoshop, Illustrator, XD	95%
Web design	70%

OTHER SKILLS:

Git, Agile, WordPress, ARCore, ARKit, Vuforia, Grandnode, Nopcommerce, Bootstrap, Website hosting, UI/UX

LANGUAGES:

Arabic - Native Tongue. English – Read and Write.

PROFILE:

Hi. I'm a software developer with 5 years of commercial experience creating successful websites and games I build Websites, I do Frontend, Back-end development, and some games. I use C#, HTML, CSS and JavaScript as main languages for work. .Net Core, Unity, React, Sass, modern JS is also part of my development stack

EDUCATION:

Syrian Virtual University:

2019-now

Master of Web Science (MWS)

Syrian Virtual University:

2015-2018

Bachelor degree in Information Technology student.

Damascus University:

2013-2014

Specialization Computer engineering -Technical Computer College.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:

Coders DC now

Full stack web developer using .NET Core and MSSQL

Smart Gate 2017-2019

Full stack web developer using .NET Core and MSSQL

Joy Gates 2016-2017

Develop and publish games for android and IOS using unity.

Projects:

CoGile

Developed a task management system to help teams work together on multiple projects beside tracking their progress and achievements

CoGit

Developed a self-hosted git server with .net core.

Plasma

Developed an api and admin panel for plasma mobile app that's help people keep track of those with Coronavirus around them

Other projects, please visit my website at hosam.xyz